PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY
64TH ARCHERY EXHIBITION MATCH
Hyeonmu House, Black Tortoise of the North!
Cheongnyong House, Azure Dragon of the East!
Jujak House, Vermilion Bird of the South!
Baekho House, White Tiger of the West!
That brat is Jujak's rep?
She's pretty good. I saw her practice.
I got this key from Ryu Minseok, Cheongnyong House, ninth grade.
She is one vicious brat.
Just last month, she couldn't even break a seven.
Why are you always so hostile toward her?
Do you like her?
A lowly creature like her?
- Are you insane? -  Ryu Minseok.
Yes?
Watch your mouth.
- Pardon? - Your vulgarity…
offends my eyes and ears.
Understood.
Let's go, Cheongnyong House!
Good luck!
Ten points!
Nine points!
My goodness.
The students' enthusiasm is truly remarkable, isn't it?
News of Your Majesty's attendance really fired them up.
Word has reached me
that the archery range was open around the clock.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It was a personal request from Grand Prince I-AN.
Cheongnyong House, you're so cool!
- Go, Cheongnyong House! - Cheongnyong!
- Cheongnyong of the East! - Cheongnyong of the East!
:cue
Nine points!
Come on…
Ten points!
It's okay. We still have one more round.
We can turn it around then.
HYEONMU, CHEONGNYONG, JUJAK, BAEKHO
It appears victory belongs to House Cheongnyong this year.
I am not so sure.
It is not over
until it is truly over.
Last round!
You got this!
- Go, Cheongnyong! - Go, Jujak!
You got this, Jujak!
Nine points!
110 POINTS
EPISODE 2
Let's…
get married.
What are the terms?
You don't seem surprised.
Why should I be?
- There must've been plenty before me. - There have.
Just in the past two days, I've received dozens of match proposals.
Damn it.
So…
state your terms. :cue
I shall personally assess them.
I have a lot of money.
I was expecting something a little more creative.
No point in wasting creativity.
Arranged marriages are all the same.
After all,
familiarity makes everything feel better,
from the food you eat, to the path you take,
even the clothes you wear.
That's why you reach for them.
So?
An assessment of the familiarity.
My pedigree is impressive, and my acumen sharper still.
I have an older brother,
but you don't need to worry.
He's too dumb to cause any trouble.
I know you don't like it when in-laws overstep.
What else?
I've got thick skin.
A successful woman and the bastard heir to a conglomerate empire.
Do you have any idea how much criticism I face every day?
Your Royal Highness would never know in a million years.
It's better that way.
And I will make sure you never find out.
So just use me
as your human shield.
Pew…
We're getting divorced once the contract is over anyway.
And even then,
I'll take the hit.
Anything else?
Beauty?
What else?
- You need more? - Yeah. What else?
Areum?
- Aide Choi. - What are you doing here?
Well, it's time for his herbal tonic.
Such perfect timing.
I can bring it to him. Give it to me.
Ah…
Your Royal Highness, it is Hyeon.
I-I have your tonic--
- Leave it there and go. - Yes, sir.
:cue
Your Majesty.
Jaegyeong of the Kim Family has arrived.
Show her in.
PERFECT CROWN
CASTLE BEAUTY
- Has Ms. Seong come in yet? - What?
Yes, she just came in.
What is it? Why are you smiling?
You don't even like me smiling now?
You shouldn't be smiling right now.
Have you lost your mind? Or are you being punished?
Is he going to force you to drink poison?
Don't be ridiculous.
This isn't the Joseon Dynasty.
Ah…
Exactly.
So what happened? Update me already.
I was rejected.
What?
I said I was rejected.
I decline.
- May I ask why? - Because there is…
…something I value more than wealth, ability, and beauty.
And what might that be?
If I tell you,
can you give it to me?
You think I can't?
So? What did he say he needs?
Love.
Huh?
He wishes to marry for love.
It's been his lifelong dream, apparently.
He's more of a romantic than you'd think.
- Romantic, my foot. - You scared me.
He's clearly just screwing with me.
So you screwed her over.
I thought you two went to the same school.
You could've just said no and politely declined her offer.
You should've been nicer.
You can be so mean.
I'll look for another candidate.
Why?
Since you were rejected.
So?
What? Are you going to try again?
Yeah.
Why? You weren't even sincere about it.
Oh, please. I couldn't be more sincere.
As if.
What kind of "sincere" person
would say, "I've got money, power, a deadbeat brother,
and I'll even sign the divorce papers"?
Not a shred of modesty to be found.
Ms. Do.
Prince I-AN is already surrounded by a horde armed with calculated modesty.
What do you think it'll take to win against them?
You need a strategy to set yourself apart.
So are you saying you intentionally pulled that crazy stunt?
I'm sure he's fond of eccentrics like me.
Birds of a feather flock together.
He showed up to His Majesty's Royal Birthday Banquet in a cheollik.
That's not "normal," is it?
Were you not set on Jaegyeong of the Kim Family? :cue
PROSPECTIVE CONSORT
I do not intend to play matchmaker.
I would rather remain a spectator.
The more people interfere, the greater the conflict grows.
In the end,
the one who staged it will emerge the winner.
Does that mean…
I must meet this maiden.
You said to prepare the new proposal by next week--
- Listen… - I'll have it by this evening.
Mm-mmm.
You can give that to me next week.
Pardon?
Then why…
You do know…
how much I rely on you,
don't you?
M-Me? Y-You rely on me?
I am aware.
With that in mind,
may I ask a small, secret favor
of you?
A secret favor?
Secret.
W-W-Why? What's wrong?
You're so out of it. What are you even looking at?
What did she say?
- She's getting married. - Huh?
Right… Wait, she's getting married?
Mom.
You know that uncle you mentioned last time?
Yeah.
Not the one who went to jail. I don't like him!
The one who works at the Royal Secretariat.
Yes, that's right.
Do you think I could get his contact information?
Goodness, Reporter Park.
It's me. Have you been well?
Yes, of course.
No, Ms. Seong is doing very well.
Yes, that's right.
So, Reporter Kim, I heard you are a royal correspondent.
Ah, in that case,
you must have connections with the Public Affairs Office as well.
Ah…
Yes, that's right.
He's taking some time off,
so no official engagements.
The Royal Guard accompanies him for all that,
- so he'd be impossible to approach. - Is that so?
However,
he's bound to have informal engagements.
As it turns out, there are a few spots he visits frequently.
I've managed to compile
a comprehensive list.
Thank you. I'll let you get back to work.
W-Wait, Ms. Do.
Am I part of Ms. Seong's circle now?
Of course.
Without a doubt.
Ah…
:cue
Hyah!
Whoa, whoa…
Hmm?
Hyah!
Seong Huiju?
Whoa…
It's been a while, Your Royal Highness.
I believe it has been two days.
Isn't it odd?
It's only been two days, but I missed you so much.
Why ride here and not at the Royal Riding Grounds?
It is too confined there.
You could feel confined here too.
Hyah!
I missed you.
Even though I saw you yesterday.
But why are you having breakfast here and not the Royal Dining Hall?
- I am taking some time off. - Oh…
Me too.
Are you off to volunteer at the cat shelter?
To see Taekwon and Taegeuk?
You dared to run a background check on me?
- Yes. - "Yes"?
You said you wanted to marry for love.
So?
So…
that is why I dare
to make a play
for Your Royal Highness's heart.
I missed you!
Where are you…
You can enjoy the movie. :cue
I'll just enjoy watching you.
I missed you.
Should we run together?
Oh!
You're pretty fast!
- What do you think? - About what?
The outfit I am wearing right now.
Well, it's not bad…
"It's not bad"? That simply won't do.
What do you mean?
Just keeps popping up out of nowhere.
What keeps popping up out of nowhere?
I must have new garments made.
What? All of a sudden?
If I'm shadowed at every turn, shouldn't I appear flawless at every step?
Wait, so who's shadowing you?
Get in.
Am I just talking to myself?
GREMLIN
What a crappy way to start the day.
What is it?
Huiju, you haven't forgotten what today is, right?
I definitely did.
That's why I'm calling to remind you.
You have your arranged date today.
Listen, Dayeong…
I guess Father has high hopes for today.
He insisted that I go to your place to help you with your outfit and makeup.
I spent ages trying to talk him out of putting that pressure on you.
How incredibly thoughtful of you.
I know, right?
Huiju, do you think you'll need my help?
I can head over there right now.
Yeah, you should go. She's going to need a lot of help.
- Taeju? - You heard that?
What are you doing? Shouldn't you be at work by now?
Huiju, I'll text you his number and the meeting place again.
Be sure to check!
You know if you bail on him,
you'll put both Father and me in a tough spot, right?
Geez, this damn Gremlin is unbelievable.
Father is threatening to shut down Castle Beauty if you bail again,
so watch out!
P.S. Kim Yeonjun.
Height, 180 cm. I hear he's really handsome too.
Mr. Kim Yeonjun?
My apologies for the last-minute changes.
I wanted to take care of this quickly.
Not at all. I know how busy you are.
I heard a lot about you from my father.
Really?
Yes, I heard
that you possess both beauty and brains.
And that you have a deep appreciation for art as well.
Hmm… I do?
Yes, don't you run an arts foundation?
Brilliantly, might I add.
Oh, that?
That's for money laundering purposes.
Brilliantly so.
Pardon? :cue
You know.
When should we hold the wedding?
September? October?
Pardon?
It's an arranged marriage anyway.
No reason to prolong it.
I see.
But shouldn't we at least--
Do you have siblings?
Only son?
Yes, I am.
I'm an only child.
Mmm…
That's nice.
No siblings to fight over the inheritance.
PRIVATE COLLECTION OF GRAND PRINCE I-AN
I have an older brother.
You know Director Seong Taeju?
Yes, I met him last time at a shareholders' meeting.
My father simply adores him.
He'll likely succeed my father as chairman.
And you're a part of that plan.
Me?
How am I a part of that?
He doesn't want to give me leverage.
I'm already good at my job.
He knows if I marry into a powerful family on top of that,
the first thing I'll do is kick my brother to the curb.
I see.
PRIVATE COLLECTION OF GRAND PRINCE I-AN
Is he a cat lover or something?
Do you think you can do it?
- Pardon? - If you're interested in marrying me,
money must be what you're after.
I can do that.
Whatever sum you have in mind,
I can give you far more than that.
What about you? Can you do your part?
Are you willing to devote all of yourself to me…
so I can get all the way to the top?
Ms. Seong?
Aide Choi.
- Hello. - Hello there.
You must be here for the exhibit.
Yes. I wanted to see for myself how impressive the Royal Collection was.
I see. Is it to your liking?
It's not bad.
I'd steal a few if I could.
Then you should go to basement level two.
The expensive stuff is there.
Aide Choi.
Coming.
Please excuse me.
Enjoy the exhibit.
I'm sorry. I should've introduced you.
Huiju.
I don't think this marriage would work.
Not the least bit surprised.
:cue
- Who? - Ms. Seong Huiju.
The one who proposed to you.
Gosh, as soon as you turned her down,
she found herself a new man.
She's so cool. So cool.
To be honest, I was worried she might be one of the Queen Mother's people.
You have quite the imagination.
Her Majesty and Seong Huiju?
Why not? It's a possibility.
"Why not"?
Move it more to the right.
More to the right?
Up.
Down.
Up, up, down.
Original spot.
My sister-in-law hails from a family that has produced four queens.
Few people truly grasp how towering that pride
and sense of superiority is.
A person like her,
colluding with Huiju, a mere commoner?
Who would win between the two?
Well, you see…
I did a little digging into Ms. Seong.
- Choi Hyeon. - I mean,
it wasn't a proper investigation or anything.
It was just a light inquiry.
You have to admit it was a bit strange.
She just showed up out of nowhere and proposed.
- So? - I found that
there was nothing special to note.
She only leaves the house to go to work.
She doesn't seem to have too many friends either.
She eats with her assistant and goes to the movies with her.
Wait!
Maybe it's because of her temper?
- Her temper? - You didn't know?
I heard she was known for being a hothead in school.
It's harder to find someone who hasn't fought her.
I hear she never lost a fight either.
Aren't you curious?
About what?
As you said, the Queen Mother and Ms. Seong
could not be any more different.
Of course, if rank is in play, the outcome is obvious.
But strip away the hierarchy?
It'll be like "Pow!" With a bit of…
My apologies.
Have you truly gone mad?
I INTEND TO STEP DOWN FROM THE THRONE…
It will be better than dying.
It would be better to die.
I would rather see you dead.
For the sake of the Crown Prince.
My Queen.
My Queen! :cue
- Fire! - It's a fire!
- Your Majesty! - Your Majesty!
Your Majesty…
Where is the Crown Prince?
Huh?
Where is my nephew…
the heir to the throne?
Did you sleep poorly again?
You can't keep going without sleep.
Do you know what you will be doing today, Your Majesty?
I am to present the Flowers of Honor.
The recipients are your valued subjects who lead the nation's industries.
They are Your Majesty's trusty workhorses.
Hence,
you must carry yourself with dignity.
When is I-AN set to return?
I believe he is to return in four days.
This is your opportunity.
You must show the world you can do it on your own.
Without I-AN by your side.
Do you understand?
Yes.
He'll be fine, right?
No, he won't.
How can you say that? You're his uncle.
I know because I'm his uncle.
I know that my nephew is but a mere child.
Then perhaps you can go and lend him your support.
- Why should I? - You said he is just a child.
Why are you sweating so much?
Are you feeling unwell?
Yes, I'm listening.
All right, I get it.
DOBBY
You have to be at the venue by 11,
so no dawdling please.
Have you eaten?
You won't have time to eat, so eat something beforehand.
There will be reporters everywhere.
A lot of eyes will be on you.
You know if you cause a scene,
I'll be stuck working all night, right?
Your dry-cleaned outfit is on the hanger.
No red.
No strong perfume.
No flashy accessories. Got it?
I bought you for this exact purpose.
Don't even. I told you nothing flashy.
Are we on a video call?
:cue
2025 ECONOMIC HONORS OF KOREA
This is how they treat their honorees?
Lower your voice. There are lots of reporters around.
Seriously? If anything, they should be boosting my morale.
Are they trying to crush it?
His Majesty the King is coming. What choice do we have?
Right, so why did he need to be here?
Just enjoy cookies at the palace.
- Stop it. - All right!
Your Majesty.
You do not need to be nervous.
You have us by your side.
Would Your Majesty like a snack?
Can we review the order of the ceremony again?
Looking at that will only make you more nervous.
Once you step up onto the podium, we'll take care of everything.
Your Majesty.
Your Royal Highness.
What brings you here?
You dare stand in my way?
No, I wasn't…
Then do you stand in His Majesty's way?
The aides have been negligent in their duties.
Both protocol and security are woefully inadequate.
My apologies, Your Royal Highness.
INCOMING CALL
Your Majesty.
Uncle.
I am scared, Uncle.
Thus,
I have come to fulfill my duty as your loyal subject, Your Majesty.
Announcing His Majesty!
:cue
Take my hand, Your Majesty.
Next, we have the Global Entrepreneur Award.
Chairman Park Jeseung. Please give him a warm round of applause.
Next, we have the Best Entrepreneur Award.
Castle Beauty's Seong Huiju.
Castle Beauty remains at the forefront of the global K-beauty craze,
showcasing Korea's advanced technology and refined beauty.
Guided by the slogan "Eco Beauty,"
they remain dedicated to creating eco-friendly products.
Your Majesty.
Can you place it on my head?
Right here.
I am deeply honored, Your Majesty.
The nation rejoices
in the beauty of your talent.
I missed you.
Will there be a prize as well?
I believe it is already on your head.
This is from His Majesty.
There is something else I would like
from Your Royal Highness.
She is a young leader representing the nation.
CEO Seong Huiju. Please give her a warm round of applause.
Ready?
- Got it? - Yes, got it.
Okay.
"Hashtag Flower of Honor."
"Best Company."
"Castle Beauty."
"Hashtag…
Grand Prince I-AN."
Let's go. :cue
PRIME MINISTER MIN JEONGWOO
Come in.
Sir.
The Economic Honors event went smoothly.
Really?
Our young Sovereign is all grown up now.
Grand Prince I-AN accompanied him.
- Isn't he on leave? - Yes.
It was a last-minute decision after His Majesty made a personal request.
Hmm…
PRINCE I-AN'S SURPRISE APPEARANCE
AT 2025 ECONOMIC HONORS…
CASTLE BEAUTY'S SEONG HUIJU RECEIVES BEST ENTREPRENEUR AWARD
Are you going somewhere?
I'm clocking out.
Already?
I'm done.
And maybe a bit quicker next time.
Pardon?
If you tell me after the fact, where does that leave me?
My apologies, sir.
Get back safely, Your Majesty.
Are you not coming with me?
I am still on leave.
Your Majesty, the Queen Mother is waiting.
Are you all right?
Take this.
This too.
- Wait, hold on. Give me that too. - Why?
Are you actually wearing that hat to your hotel staycation?
- Yeah. - Seriously?
Don't tell people you're the CEO of Castle Beauty.
They all know already.
Don't call me unless it's urgent.
It's been ages since I've had time off.
Me too. Me too.
- Go. - I'm off.
Seong Huiju.
Oh.
Jeongwoo.
Order everything.
I am a winner of the Flower of Honor.
It'll be my treat today. :cue
No.
Let me treat you today to congratulate you.
I told you I'd treat you last time.
Now that's an offer I never turn down.
Score.
Hmm…
Just take it off for the meal.
Why?
Jealous?
It's embarrassing.
You look like a giant pineapple.
Are you sure it's not a really pretty pineapple?
Definitely not.
Moments like this remind me you haven't changed at all.
What do you mean?
You used to get the Flower of Honor all the time in school.
For your grades and artwork…
What else was there?
Archery?
Archery.
How were you even chosen to represent Jujak House?
I had to change my grip yesterday…
Activate your core.
Chin down.
Chest.
Draw your bow.
Shoulders back further.
Right by your lips.
Focus!
Right. Focus.
I swear
there will be hell to pay if we lose because of you.
- Focus! - Huh?
Right, focus.
Keep pulling
and shoot.
Thank goodness you were at least book smart.
- Me? - You're bad at everything else.
Seriously? Me?
You're not like running the country into the ground or anything, right?
If something feels off,
don't be afraid to ask questions. No need to feel embarrassed.
Don't try to do it alone.
All right.
Just order already.
Let's see here.
What should I have? :cue
PHARMACY
Hello.
Welcome.
What should someone take if they have a really bad headache,
a slight fever, and keep breaking out in a cold sweat?
Just a moment. I'll grab what you need.
Okay. Please hurry.
Your Royal Highness.
Once the fever breaks,
we should take you to Royal Seoul Hospital.
I think it'd be best to have you checked out there.
It's crawling with the Queen Mother's brothers.
Don't stir up trouble.
Understood.
Have you notified my household?
Yes.
I told them you'd be staying the night at a hotel.
I didn't say anything about you being sick. Don't worry.
The doors are opening.
SHE LOOKS SO DAMN GOOD
Our stock is going to skyrocket tomorrow.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my.
- Ms. Seong? - Aide Choi?
- Hello. - Yes, hello.
You don't need to worry too much.
However, I do wonder if he typically has trouble sleeping.
Uh…
Yes, he suffers from a bit of insomnia.
It's hard to recover from fatigue if you can't sleep.
Sleeping aids should help.
Make sure he gets a prescription and gets some sleep.
All right. Thank you, doctor.
Doctor.
Thank you for coming at a late hour.
No need to thank me.
For the record,
can we say I was the patient today?
- Pardon? - You know I get hurt all the time.
You were here to see me
and only me today.
Understood, Ms. Seong.
Get back safely.
Take care.
PRINCE I-AN'S SURPRISE APPEARANCE
AT ECONOMIC HONORS…
Did you forget I told you to carry yourself with dignity?
U-Uncle…
Do not call him that!
Please do not let it upset you.
His Majesty is still very young.
How truly contemptible.
Pardon?
I speak of that feeble bloodline.
He was the very likeness of the late king at that moment.
It sends a chill down my spine.
Have you located I-AN?
Yes, Your Majesty. :cue
Aide Choi.
Ms. Seong.
You need to eat.
How about a sandwich?
SUBWAY
I see you really like sandwiches.
Not exactly.
I was so preoccupied earlier that I didn't get a chance to eat.
And this is really good.
Eat up.
I order this all the time when I'm working late.
Thank you.
He was just on the verge of collapse earlier.
My mind went blank.
You were a huge help.
But wouldn't he be better off returning to the palace?
There are physicians at the palace.
I'm sure that will be more comfortable than staying in some hotel room.
He despises being the center of attention.
The physicians would freak out if they knew.
The Royal Medical Institution would be on standby all day.
The Royal Kitchen would be cooking all sorts of soups and porridges.
Royal Seoul Hospital would be the same. It'd be worse if anything.
As soon as he steps inside,
photos will be taken, and all kinds of rumors will spread.
Hmm…
Oh, no.
- You need to go. - What?
The Queen Mother is here.
- Get up. - Who? Mother?
You need to get out of here. The Queen Mother…
- Where can I hide you? Come on. - What's going on?
- Where are you taking me? - You have to be quiet.
You can do this. You got this, Choi Hyeon.
- Your Majesty, what brings you by? - Step aside.
It is already quite late. Tomorrow…
Tell her I am not yet suitably attired
and that she must wait.
When the day breaks, get yourself suitably attired
to answer for today's transgression.
That is what you will tell him.
What now? :cue
- Yeah? -  Ms. Seong, where are you?
Ms. Do, do you know what time it is right now?
Where are you?
At the hotel.
- Stay right there. - What?
Stay in your room. I'll come to you.
Got it?
What's wrong with her?
PRINCE I-AN SPOTTED IN SECRET TRYST
WITH CASTLE BEAUTY SEONG HUIJU
WHERE THE ROYAL COUPLE ENJOYS THEIR TIME OFF…
…A SECRET DATE AT A HOTEL…
ROYAL PAIR ROCKS…
PRINCE I-AN'S SECRET LOVER…
- No, no. -  Yes, Reporter Kim.
- I'll get back to you. - No, we haven't confirmed anything yet.
- Yes, will do. - No, not at all.
- Just a moment. - Hello?
Is Seong Huiju insane?
- Why? What's up? - Look at this.
WEDDING BELLS…
Oh my goodness!
- Do you think they slept together? - Of course, they were at a hotel!
Ooh…
What are you so happy about?
What? Are you jealous of her?
You are unbelievable.
Ah… Is that why she turned down all those dates?
You think so?
"Grand Prince I-AN's secret lover"?
Me?
Pull yourself together, Do Hyejeong. You've been through far worse.
You got this. Damn it.
Calm down.
Who'd believe this crap?
Why wouldn't they?
Ms. Seong.
Look. They have photos.
Prince I-AN checks in at 4:00 p.m. Snap.
You check in at 7:00 p.m. Snap.
You step out at 9:00 p.m.
to return at 9:30 p.m. with sandwiches. Snap.
And you can even see where you got the sandwiches from.
- Really? - Yes.
Wow. That sandwich place just hit the jackpot.
They should pay us for the PR.
Ms. Seong.
All right. I hear you.
But I swear nothing happened.
We were with Aide Choi and stuff.
Oh, I see.
Who cares about that when Aide Choi isn't in a single shot?
Not even a single royal guard.
What a great narrative.
"Prince I-AN Dismisses Royal Guards for Secret Tryst."
From the riding grounds
to a traditional restaurant,
all sorts of location shoots for you.
SEONGSAN DAILY REPORTER AN SAEHUN
HAEMYEONG REPORTER JEONG SUJIN
First of all, why did you call for your doctor?
They got him too?
Thanks to that shot, they're even speculating you're pregnant.
What?
Wow…
You have to hand it to the public's imagination.
"A premarital pregnancy"?
Focus!
Focus.
Are you sure it will be all right?
I fear this may bring dishonor to the Crown.
I am sure it will.
The royal family's dignity will be cast to the ground…
and this woman will be laid upon the chopping block and carved up.
That must be why…
they are denying it.
Are you doing this
because you don't know who Prince I-AN is for the people?
Did you already forget last year when you dated the leader
of Idol Galaxy or whatever and got egged when you were caught?
They keyed your car every other day.
You said it was pure torture dealing with the overzealous fans
who rang your doorbell at dawn and ran away.
You must remember that.
Prince I-AN isn't an idol star.
He's so much worse.
Idol stars are beloved by their fandom alone.
Prince I-AN is beloved by the whole country.
Everyone.
I don't love him.
Ms. Seong!
You're going to scare the baby!
"A premarital pregnancy"?
Unbelievable.
Right. Got it. :cue
GRAND PRINCE
SEONG HUIJU
The caller is unavailable…
Sir.
Still, wouldn't it be best to contain this quickly?
If people start throwing around terms like "Royal Risk"…
- It won't be all bad. - Pardon?
It'll make all the criticism over the minimum wage freeze disappear.
Leave it for now. It's just a minor fuss.
Yes, sir.
To the palace, please.
To my private residence.
You need to make your way to the palace first.
Prime Minister Min is already there.
The Public Affairs Office is also looking--
I said, to my private residence.
Have Seong Huiju…
meet me there.
This way, Ms. Seong.
Am I the only one freaking out?
No. I'm freaking out too.
Only Ms. Seong may go inside.
His Royal Highness asked for a private meeting.
I'm fine. Just wait for me here.
Is your fever gone?
As you can see.
You're in good spirits.
I missed you. Even though I saw you yesterday.
Let me apologize
for dragging you into this scandal
and letting you become the scapegoat for it.
All of it.
So?
Tell me what you desire.
If I tell you,
can you give it to me?
Seong Huiju.
What I desire
may be terribly difficult to attain.
Let me get this straight.
That woman and His Royal Highness are actually an item?
Didn't they seem like they had nothing going on last time she visited?
A secret rendezvous at a hotel? That's a done deal.
Still, don't you think it's a bit weird?
His Royal Highness is so busy.
When did he have time to date?
Areum.
I've told you a hundred times.
When people say they can't date because they're too busy,
it's just an excuse.
Do you remember? :cue
It's a Flower of Honor.
The one I received after I beat you.
Seven points!
109 POINTS
Didn't feel like crap?
It felt like crap to me.
Losing to someone
who I could have beaten.
My brother is an idiot.
He got kicked out of the school we made a donation to.
He even managed to tank a business that would've run on its own.
But my father and the board
are always dying to replace me with him
whenever I make the slightest mistake.
As if they've been biding their time.
Why do you think that is?
Because he was born before me?
Because he's a son? And a legitimate heir?
Oh…
Perhaps it's because he married into a noble family.
That's why…
I'm looking to marry up.
You would marry me for nothing more
than a hollow title?
Because I've lost countless opportunities simply for not having that title.
Prepare yourself to become the Grand Prince's wife.
You will be up against…
…the whole nation.
PERFECT CROWN
Your Royal Highness, is your scandal with CEO Seong Huiju true?
The top five trending key words are all about you.
He's even a good actor.
You're really going to marry him?
I have to marry him right now.
Stay away from His Royal Highness!
She will be staying here for the time being.
An investigation is required.
Cooperate with the Junghwajeon Hall fire investigation, please.
It's fine.
I'm used to going up against people like that.
I must appear insanely infatuated with you
for people to believe
this absurd marriage is genuine.
PERFECT CROWN
Translated by Justin S. Kim